<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Freddy&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://fredericmrozinski.github.io/built-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Freddy&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.131.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 13:12:10 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://fredericmrozinski.github.io/built-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> Jade Scientific Calculator - Past, Present, and Future</title>
      <link>https://fredericmrozinski.github.io/built-blog/posts/jsc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 13:12:10 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fredericmrozinski.github.io/built-blog/posts/jsc/</guid>
      <description>Jade Scientific Calculator - Past, Present, and Future Jade Scientific Calculator (JSC) is an Android application designed for advanced mathematical calculations, yet simple enough to be a daily tool for basic computations. From basic arithmetic to solving differential equations and linear algebra problems, this app has you covered.
Past - Eager Development and the Pandemic JSC began as my capstone project in high school. During my AP courses, I fell in love with my HP Prime calculator but grew frustrated that our phones, despite their phenomenal hardware, lacked an equally good and user-friendly app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor-Series based pruning criteria for weight pruning in neural networks</title>
      <link>https://fredericmrozinski.github.io/built-blog/posts/neuron-pruning-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fredericmrozinski.github.io/built-blog/posts/neuron-pruning-1/</guid>
      <description>Summary This article discusses how the Taylor series motivates two commonly used pruning criteria for neural networks, namely
Magnitude based pruning Fisher information based pruning The motivation for this blogpost is to highlight that those pruning criteria are closely related while having different bounds on the resulting errors after pruning. I created this blogpost because I found this information lacking in many papers that used the concepts introduced below.
Introduction A common fully-connected neural network - as the name suggests - possesses &amp;ldquo;synapses&amp;rdquo;, i.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
